there to do something with that, you know, we have a young congressman that's right now
in jail for lying about where he went to college and other things. It was, you know, frankly
not good. It was pretty bad. But it was nothing compared to Blumenthal. I mean, what Blumenthal
did, he was for 20 years a hero, a great war hero. And then he sits back and, you know,
sanctimonious kind of a guy, looks down, how dare you do this to the American public, you
know. What a fake. But I thought Pam was incredible yesterday, as well as Secretary
Christine Ohm, who's really out there courageously, and I appreciate it, Christie, amazing what
you're doing. FBI Director Cash Patel, who's really coming up with some great information,
Cash. It's great. Keep it coming, because there's plenty of it. Deputy Attorney General,
one of the best lawyers you'll ever find. Todd Blanch, who I know personally is a good
lawyer, because I'm here. Thank you very much, Todd. Good job, Todd. Let me ask Attorney
General Bondi to say a few words, and then we'll follow it up with Secretary Ohm and
Director Patel, and we're going to have some of the people around the table, very courageous
people, and they're going to be talking, journalists almost all, and they're going to be talking,
and it will take some questions from the press at the end. Okay, Pam, please. Thank
you, President Trump, and as you made clear, Antifa is a domestic, left-wing terrorist
organization. We've seen them on video for years, because they wanted to be seen, and
they got away with it. They beat journalists, they attack courthouses, they attack police
stations, they dox and assault our law enforcement officers. The Biden administration let them
commit these crimes with total impunity for years. So did Democrat leaders like Pritzker
and Mayor Brandon Johnson. Last week, independent journalist Nick Sorter was arrested just for
protecting himself against Antifa. I saw it online, and I called Nick. I couldn't believe
what happened. He did all this just trying to save our American flag from being burned.
He was pushed down and assaulted, yet the local police arrested Nick, not the Antifa
thugs who did this to him. Antifa feels empowered to operate in the open, because weak Democrats
have turned a blind eye to their actions. Their hatred for President Trump and for law
and order agendas fuels their violence. We've seen more than 1,000%, 1,000% increase in
attacks against our ICE agents since January 20th. Secretary Noem is out there fighting
for you firsthand to keep our federal officers safe, to keep our federal buildings safe,
and we're not going to have it anymore, these thugs. We saw what's happening in Portland
and Chicago, and you saw what happened in Dallas. No longer. This is not activism, it's
anarchy. We can't and we will not let masked terrorists burn our buildings, attack our
law enforcement, and intimidate our communities. Under your leadership, President Trump, we're
deploying the full might of the federal law enforcement to crack down on Antifa and other
domestic terrorist organizations led by Stephen Miller. And Stephen, thank you for everything
you're doing. Last week, I issued a memo ordering our federal law enforcement agents, DEA, FBI,
U.S. Marshals, and ATF to protect ICE officers from Antifa and other radical left-wing violence.
Director Patel has been going nonstop. He and Deputy Attorney General Blanche were in
Chicago yesterday. Yesterday. While Secretary Noem was in Portland, we are around this country
fighting against this domestic terrorism. We had Apple and Google take down the ICE
block apps, hope they continue to comply with that, threatening the safety of our federal
law enforcement officers. We're not going to stop at just arresting the violent criminals
we can see in the streets. Fighting crime is more than just getting the bad guy off the streets.
It's breaking down the organization brick by brick, just like we did with cartels. We're
going to take the same approach, President Trump, with Antifa. Destroy the entire organization
from top to bottom.